Hubungi

septiawanindra554@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/indraseptiawan- (LinkedIn)

Certifications

Browser-based Models with TensorFlow.js

Introduction to Git and GitHub

Belajar Dasar Visualisasi Data

Memulai Dasar Pemrograman untuk Menjadi Pengembang Software

Unsupervised Learning, Recommenders, Reinforcement Learning

Indra Septiawan

Machine Learning Student at Bangkit Academy 2023

Tulungagung, Jawa Timur, Indonesia

Ringkasan

Indra is a creative problem solver, able to think analytically, and has good communication skills. he

believes that the application of machine learning in data science and analysis can have a positive

impact on decision-making and optimizing business processes. indra is ready to face new challenges

in the fields of science, data analysis, and machine learning, and contribute to the achievement of

company goals by combining technical expertise and an understanding of scientific concepts.

Pengalaman

PT. KIMIA FARMA, TBK Big Data Analytics Juni 2023 - Present (1 bulan)

- Data Warehouse, SQL Querying, Big Data Processing and Scheduling
- Data Analysis Statistics
- Data Visualization with Google Data Studio

Home Credit Indonesia
Data Scientist
Juni 2023 - Present (1 bulan)

- Able to master and implement various skills and tools such as Big Data Fundamentals, Statistics & Data

Analytics, SQL Querying, R Programming, Python Programming, Machine Learning.

- Complete end-to-end Machine Learning modeling to create data science solutions for clients.

Bangkit Academy led by Google, Tokopedia, Gojek, & Traveloka Machine Learning Student Februari 2023 - Present (5 bulan)

Learn the key concepts and applications of AI to solve a wide range of ML problems with these specializations: Google IT Automation with Python, Google Data Analytics, Math for Machine Learning, Machine Learning Specialization, DeepLearning.AI TensorFlow Developer Professional Certificate, DeepLearning.AI Tensorflow Data and Deployment, and TensorFlow Certification Preparation.

BTPN Syariah

Data Engineer

Mei 2023 - Mei 2023 (1 bulan)

- Learned Storaged Procedure and Trigger in SQL Programming
- Made the ERD Diagram and many relations for several tables.
- Learned data Visualization using Tableau

id/x partners

Data Scientist

Mei 2023 - Mei 2023 (1 bulan)

- Business Understanding
- Analytical Approach
- Data Storytelling
- Exploratory Data Analysis
- Data Visualization
- Machine Learning

ASEAN Foundation

ASEAN Data Science Explorers 2023

April 2023 - April 2023 (1 bulan)

Jakarta Raya, Indonesia

- Data Modeling
- Smart Discovery
- Designer Mode
- Data Explorer Mode
- Styling

Kampus Merdeka

WMK BINUS 2022 Road to GLOBAL Beellionaire.

Agustus 2022 - Januari 2023 (6 bulan)

Jakarta Barat, Jakarta Raya, Indonesia

Google Workspace · Figma · Miro Collaboration Platform · Problem Solving · Pitching Ideas

Pendidikan

Universitas Tulungagung Gelar Sarjana, Akuntansi